Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
- RG 39.74. Medical College Christian Association, 1906
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1906 (Box 395, Folder 11)
- RG 39.75. NYU College Bowl, 1987-1989
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1989 (Box 395, Folder 12)
- RG 39.76. Retailing Club, 1940
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1940 (Box 395, Folder 13)
- RG 39.77. International Business Association, 1988-1989
  - IBA Notebook, 1988-1989 (Box 395, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988-1989 (Box 395, Folder 15)
- RG 39.78. Science Fiction Club, 1988-1995
  - Pulsar, 1988-2005 (Box 395, Folder 16-18, Box 396, Folder 1)
- RG 39.80. Hotel Sales Marketing Association International (HSMAI) NYU Student Chapter, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 2)
- RG 39.81. Greater Retailing Association, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 3)
- RG 39.82. Hong Kong Student Association, 1988-1989
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988-1989 (Box 396, Folder 4)
- RG 39.83. Chinese Mei Society, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 5)
- RG 39.84. Chinese Christian Fellowship, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 6)
- RG 39.85. Students for Life, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 7)
- RG 39.86. Social and Athletic Club, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 8)
- RG 39.87. Minority Journalist Society, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 9)
- RG 39.88. Model United Nations Debate Club, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 10)
- RG 39.89. Martial Arts Society, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 11)
- RG 39.90. Tae Kwon Do Karate Club, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 12)
- RG 39.91. The NYU News and Letters Youth Committee, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 13)
- RG 39.92. Young Republicans / NYU College Republicans, 1988, 2019
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988, 2019 (Box 396, Folder 14)
- RG 39.93. Mock Trial Club, 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 15)
- RG 39.94. Student AIDS Coalition (S.A.C.), 1988
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 16)
- RG 39.95. Political Resource Committee, 1989-1992
  - N.Y. View, 1989-1992 (Box 419, Folder 4-7)
- RG 39.96. Clio: The Graduate Student History Association of NYU, 1989-1990
  - Graduate History Student Association Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 396, Folder 17)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 396, Folder 18-19)
- RG 39.97. F-Stop Photography Club, 1989-1998
  - F-Stop, 1989-1998 (Box 396, Folder 20-21)
- RG 39.98. The Voice Party, 1967
  - Focus, 1967 (Box 342, Folder 3)
- RG 39.99. The Classical Society, 1955
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1955 (Box 396, Folder 22)
- RG 39.100. Korean Students Association, 1990-1995
  - Bibimbap, 1995 (Box 396, Folder 23)
  - Han-Mah-Dang, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 396, Folder 24, Box 397, Folder 1)
  - HKSA New York University Monthly Newsletter, 1995 (Box 397, Folder 2)
  - KSA Bulletin, 1990 (Box 397, Folder 3)
  - Memory, 1994-1995 (Box 397, Folder 4)
- RG 39.101. Men in Finance Club, 1947, 1949, 1976-1977
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1947, 1949, 1976-1977 (Box 397, Folder 5-6)
- RG 39.102. NYU Chance, 1990-2019
  - Papercut, 1990-1991 (Box 397, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 397, Folder 8)
- RG 39.103. Central American Solidarity Committee of NYU, 1984-1992
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1984-1992 (Box 397, Folder 9)
- RG 39.104. Socialist Party / Solidarity at NYU, 1984-1991
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1984-1991 (Box 397, Folder 10)
- RG 39.105. Students for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (SETA), undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 397, Folder 11)
- RG 39.106. Seekers Christian Conference (NYU Chapter), undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 397, Folder 12)
- RG 39.107. League of Unified and Cooperative Hispanic Americans, 1979, 1982, 1995-1996, undated
  - Impacto Latino, 1995-1996 (Box 397, Folder 13)
  - The N.Y.U. Hispanic Quarterly, 1979 (Box 397, Folder 14)
  - Ritmos, 1982 (Box 397, Folder 15)
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, undated (Box 397, Folder 16)
- RG 39.108. The Fortnightly Club, 1932-1935
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1932-1935 (Box 397, Folder 17)
- RG 39.109. The Washington Square College Players, 1921-1929
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1921-1929 (Box 397, Folder 18)
- RG 39.110. The League of Women, 1931-1935
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1931-1935 (Box 397, Folder 19)
- RG 39.111. Channel Bulletin, 1982
  - Channel Bulletin, 1982 (Box 397, Folder 20)
- RG 39.113. Fauchardian Society, 1976-1989
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1976-1989 (Box 397, Folder 21)
- RG 39.114. Caducean Society, 1958, 1980
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1958, 1980 (Box 397, Folder 22)
- RG 39.115. New Ink, 1990-1998
  - New Ink, 1990-1998 (Box 398, Folder 1-4)
- RG 39.116. Pressure Points, 1993-1994
  - Pressure Points, 1993-1994 (Box 398, Folder 5)
- RG 39.117. Punchline, 1994-1996
  - Punchline, 1994-1996 (Box 398, Folder 6)
- RG 39.118. The Marketing Society, 1982, 1995-1996
  - The 4 P's, 1982 (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - The Marketing Society News, 1995-1996 (Box 400, Folder 1)
- RG 39.119. Asian Initiative at NYU, 1995
  - Asian Initiative, 1995 (Box 400, Folder 2)
- RG 39.120. Sangria Españole at NYU, 1996
  - Sangria Españole at NYU, 1996 (Box 400, Folder 3)
- RG 39.121. Arab Club, 1976-1977
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1976-1977 (Box 400, Folder 4-5)
- RG 39.123. Muslim Progressive Alliance, 1991-1993
  - The Straight Path, 1991-1993 (Box 400, Folder 6)
- RG 39.124. Graduate Economics Society, 1994-1997
  - The Student Litigator, 1994-1997 (Box 400, Folder 7)
- RG 39.125. realizASIAN, 1996-1997
  - realizASIAN, 1996-1997 (Box 400, Folder 8)
- RG 39.126. South Asian Student Association, 1992-1993
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1992-1993 (Box 400, Folder 9)
- RG 39.127. Sailing Club, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 400, Folder 10)
- RG 39.128. NYU Students for Environmental Activism, 1989-1992
  - Earth Matters, 1989-1992 (Box 400, Folder 11)
- RG 39.129. Israel Alliance, 1984
  - Manna, 1984 (Box 400, Folder 12)
- RG 39.130. Primal Scream, 1982
  - Primal Scream, 1982 (Box 419, Folder 8)
- RG 39.131. The Money Marketeers, 1990-1991
  - Sylvan Muse, 1990-1991 (Box 400, Folder 13)
- RG 39.132. Central American Solidarity Committee, 1984
  - NYU Central American Solidarity Committee, 1984 (Box 400, Folder 14)
- RG 39.133. NYU Pre Law, 1975-1979
  - From the Files, 1976-1977 (Box 400, Folder 15)
  - Pre-Law Journal, 1979 (Box 400, Folder 16)
  - Pre Law News, 1977 (Box 400, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Law Society, 1977 (Box 400, Folder 18)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1975 (Box 400, Folder 19)
- RG 39.134. Psychology Association, 1931-1936, 1963-1965
  - Psi Chi Psychology, 1931-1936 (Box 401, Folder 1-3)
  - Psi Chi Psychoscope, 1963-1965 (Box 401, Folder 4)
- RG 39.135. AH@ Freshman (later Sophomore) Society, 1898-1911
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1898-1911 (Box 401, Folder 5)
- RG 39.136. Sync Magazine, 1997-1998
  - Sync, 1997-1998 (Box 401, Folder 6)
- RG 39.137. The NYU Film Review, 1998
  - The New York University Film Review, 1998 (Box 401, Folder 7)
- RG 39.138. Graduate Student Union, 2003
  - GSOC Journal, 2003 (Box 401, Folder 8)
- RG 39.139. Universal Economics Group, 1990
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 9)
- RG 39.140. Bole (Literary Journal), 1993
  - Bole, 1993 (Box 401, Folder 10)
- RG 39.141. SansCrit, 1991
  - SansCrit, 1991 (Box 401, Folder 11)
- RG 39.142. In This Place (Literary Journal), 1995
  - In This Place, 1995 (Box 401, Folder 12)
- RG 39.143. Cogito, 1996
  - Cogito, 1996 (Box 401, Folder 13)
- RG 39.144. The Commentator, 1984-1987
  - The Commentator, 1984-1987 (Box 419, Folder 9-11, Box 420, Folder 1)
- RG 39.145. La Marche Futile, 1996-1997
  - La Marche Futile, 1996-1997 (Box 402, Folder 1)
- RG 39.146. Access @ NYU, 1997
  - Access, 1997 (Box 420, Folder 2)
- RG 39.147. The Bastard Child (of Art and Commerce), 1996
  - The Bastard Child (of Art and Commerce), 1996 (Box 402, Folder 2)
- RG 39.148. The Journal of Politics and International Affairs, 2005-2019, 2023-ongoing
  - The Journal of Politics and International Affairs, 2005-2017 (Box 153, Folder 3-6)
  - The Journal of Politics and International Affairs, 2019 (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - The Journal of Politics and International Affairs, June 2023-ongoing
    The Journal of Politics and International Affairs at New York University is a student-run publication that publishes articles, op-eds, interviews, and essays on topics in the domestic and international political landscape. The publication dates back to 2008.
- RG 39.149. Humanus, 2004-2010
  - HumaNews, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Humanus, 2004-2010 (Box 402, Folder 5-6)
- RG 39.150. Journal of Global Affairs, 2006-2007
  - Journal of Global Affairs, 2006-2007 (Box 402, Folder 7)
- RG 39.151. Baedeker: NYU's Student Travel Publication, 2005-2019
  - Baedeker, 2005-2019 (Box 402, Folder 7, Box 403, Folder 1-2)
- RG 39.152. The Medical Dialogue Review, 2007-2024
  - The Medical Dialogue Review, 2007-2019 (Box 403, Folder 3-8)
  - The Medical Dialogue Review, March-May 2024
    The Medical Dialogue Review contains peer-reviewed articles and artwork by students on the intersection of humanities and natural sciences. Topics include ethics and medicine; history and medicine; religion and medicine; arts and medicine; poetry and medicine; medicine and politics; medicine and economics; anthropology and medicine; psychology and medicine; community health; international health; health education; brand experience design; health policy; and health administration. The publication also includes interviews with medical humanity experts and undergraduate research. The earliest articles on the website date from 2016.
- RG 39.153. Raices, 2006-2007
  - Raices, 2006-2007 (Box 404, Folder 1)
- RG 39.154. Seed at NYU, 2005-2007, 2010, 2013-2017
  - Seed, 2005-2007, 2010, 2013-2017 (Box 404, Folder 2-4)
- RG 39.155. GenerAsian, 2002-2022
  - GenerAsian, 2002-2022 (Box 404, Folder 5-7)
- RG 39.156. The Management Club, 1942
  - Production, 1942 (Box 404, Folder 8)
- RG 39.157. AFTAB, NYU Muslim Student Publication, 2004-2006, 2009-2019
  - AFTAB, 2004-2006, 2009-2019 (Box 404, Folder 9-10, Box 405, Folder 1-2)
- RG 39.158. Anamesa, 2003
  - Anamesa, 2003 (Box 405, Folder 3)
- RG 39.159. Washington Square, 2002
  - Washington Square, 2002 (Box 405, Folder 4)
- RG 39.160. Simulacrum, 2005
  - Simulacrum, 2005 (Box 405, Folder 5)
- RG 39.161. The Guillotine (Literary Journal), 2008-2013
  - The Guillotine, 2008-2013 (Box 405, Folder 6-7)
- RG 39.162. Minetta Review, 1975-2017
  - Minetta Review, 1975-2017 (Box 113, Folder 4-9, Box 114, Folder 1-7, Box 115, Folder 1-6, Box 116, Box 117, Folder 1-5, Box 118, Folder 1-2)
  - Minetta Review Poster, 1988-1989 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Minetta Review, 2013-2017 (Box 399, Folder 5-8)
- RG 39.163. The Secret Weapon, 2007
  - The Secret Weapon, 2007 (Box 405, Folder 8)
- RG 39.164. Brownstone, 2007-2008
  - Brownstone, 2007-2008 (Box 405, Folder 9)
- RG 39.165. NYCHIC, Fashion Business Publication, 2008
  - NYCHIC, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 1)
- RG 39.166. Mercer Street / Expository Writing Program, 2004-2005, 2008-2009, 2023-ongoing
  - Expository Writing Program Publications, June 2023-ongoing
    Website contains back issues of the two publications of the Expository Writing program, Mercer Street and West Fourth. The issues date back to 2010.
  - Mercer Street, 2004-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 406, Folder 2-5)
  - West Fourth, June 2023-ongoing
    West Fourth is made up of essays from College Writing Workshops offered by Expository Writing program in conjunction with NYU's Pre-College Program.
- RG 39.167. Phi Alpha Theta / The Historian, 2003-2016
  - The Historian, 2003-2024 (Box 406, Folder 6-7, Box 407, Folder 1-7, Box 408, Folder 1, Box 441, Folder 1-6)
- RG 39.169. N.Y.U. Law Review, 1990-1992, 1996
  - N.Y.U. Law Review, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box 408, Folder 2)
- RG 39.170. New York University Daily Snooze / Daily Snooze, 1925
  - New York University Daily Snooze, 1925 (Box 420, Folder 3)
- RG 39.171. The Commerce Ledger, 1928
  - The Commerce Ledger, 1928 (Box 420, Folder 3)
- RG 39.172. The University in Review, 1970
  - The University in Review, 1970 (Box 420, Folder 3)
- RG 39.173. Heights Daily Nose, 1972
  - Heights Daily Nose, 1972 (Box 420, Folder 3)
- RG 39.177. Comic Book League, 2010, 2014-2015
  - Comic Book League, 2010, 2014-2015 (Box 408, Folder 3-4)
- RG 39.178. Washington Square News, 2001
  Related Materials
  A full run of this publication can be found in the finding aid for the collection: New York University Archives Collection of the Washington Square News, RG.39.178
  - Washington Square News, 2001 (Box 420, Folder 4)
- RG 39.179. Disorientation Guide, 2015, undated
  - GSOC Disorientation Guide, 2015 (Box 408, Folder 5)
  - Student and Labor Action Movement, undated (Box 408, Folder 6)
- RG 39.181. Platypus, 2007-2018
  - Platypus, 2007-2011 (Box 408, Folder 7, Box 409, Folder 1)
  - Platypus Review, 2011-2018 (Box 409, Folder 2-3)
- RG 39.182. The Headless Society, 2012-2019
  - The Guillotine, 2012-2019 (Box 409, Folder 4-5)
- RG 39.184. International Youth and Students for Social Equality (IYSSE), 2016-2018
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2016-2018 (Box 409, Folder 6)
- RG 39.188. NYU Liberation Front (publication titled Bentré), 1970-1971
  - Bentré, 1970-1971 (Box 420, Folder 4)
- RG 39.195. The Gallatin Review, 2022-ongoing
  - The Gallatin Review, May 2022-ongoing
    Gallatin Review, a student-edited journal of student writing and visual art.
- RG 39.196. The Literacy Review, 2022-ongoing
  - The Literacy Review, May 2022-ongoing
    The Literacy Review is an annual journal of writing from adult literacy programs throughout New York City. Edited by Gallatin students, the book is distributed at a celebration that includes readings by the newly published writers.
  - The Literacy Review, May 2022-ongoing
- RG 39.197. Confluence, 2022-ongoing
  - Confluence, May 2022-ongoing
    Confluence is an online platform for student writing, art, and research at NYU's Gallatin School of Individualized Study. The work published on the site comes from teacher-nominated written and art works generated in courses, and independent projects commissioned by the student editors, as well as from the undergraduate student publications, exhibits curated in the Gallatin Galleries, and visual art and performances produced for the Gallatin Arts Festival.
- RG 39.198. Embodied, 2022-ongoing
  - Embodied Magazine, May 2022-ongoing
    Embodied Magazine, launched in 2013, is a Gallatin publication that applies an "interdisciplinary approach to culture, openly exploring style and art, with the belief that doing so heightens understanding, and does not diminish intellect." The website includes op-eds on political, social, technological, and environmental developments and their impact on culture; poetry; art, food and style criticism; book, music, film, and television reviews; and playlists.
- RG 39.202. NYU, Inc., 2002-2003
  - NYU, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 420, Folder 5)
- RG 39.204. Cold Duck, 1971-1973
  - Cold Duck, 1971-1973 (Box 413, Folder 1-2, Box 420, Folder 6-7)
- RG 39.205. Varieties, 1941-1952
  - Varieties, 1941-1952 (Box 342, Folder 4-7, Box 416, Folder 1-5)
- RG 39.206. Square, 1924-1925
  - Square, 1924-1925 (Box 409, Folder 7)
- RG 39.207. Stylus, 1901-1902
  - The Stylus, 1901-1902 (Box 410, Folder 1-3)
- RG 39.208. Violet Review, 1963-1964
  - The Violet Review, 1963-1964 (Box 410, Folder 4-5)
- RG 39.209. The Arch, 1921-1930
  - The Arch, 1921-1930 (Box 410, Folder 6, Box 411, Folder 1-5, Box 412, Folder 1-6)
- RG 39.214. Economics Review, 2018
  - The Economics Review, 2018 (Box 413, Folder 3)
- RG 39.215. Undergraduate Law Review at NYU, 2018-2019
  - The Undergraduate Law Review at NYU, 2018-2019 (Box 413, Folder 4)
- RG 39.217. NYU Divest, undated
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, undated (Box 413, Folder 5)
- RG 39.219. NYU Law Students for Economic Justice, 2015
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2015 (Box 413, Folder 6)
- RG 39.220. Incarceration to Education Coalition, undated
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, undated (Box 413, Folder 7)
- RG 39.221. University Quarterly, 1878-1895
  - University Quarterly, 1878-1895 (Box 413, Folder 8-11, Box 414, Folder 1-7, Box 415, Folder 1-4)
- RG 39.222. Etc. Magazine, 1980
  - Etc. Magazine, 1980 (Box 415, Folder 5)
- RG 39.223. Real Magazine, 1992
  - Real Magazine, 1992 (Box 415, Folder 6)
- RG 39.224. Poetry Club / Life Distilled (Publication), 2010
  - Life Distilled, 2010 (Box 415, Folder 7)
- RG 39.225. The Concubine, undated
  - The Concubine, undated (Box 415, Folder 8)
- RG 39.226. University Item, 1895-1897
  - University Item, 1895-09-26-1897-04-29 (Box 432, Folder 1-6)
    Volume II No. 1 through Volume III No. 23
- RG 39.228. MYCRO, 2023
  - Issue 01, 2023 (Box Shared University Archives 149, Folder 8)
- RG 40.1.3. NYU Alumni Fund, 1985-1986, 2002-2003
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1985-1986, 2002-2003 (Box 415, Folder 9)
- RG 40.1.7. Almost Alumni News, 2007
  - Almost Alumni News, 2007 (Box 420, Folder 8)
- RG 40.7. Alumni Federation, circa 1937, 1952, 1970-1992
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, circa 1937, 1952, 1970-1992 (Box 415, Folder 10, Box 421, Folder 1-3)
- RG 40.18. University College of Arts and Science, 1987-1992
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1987-1992 (Box 421, Folder 4)
- RG 40.19. Washington Square College / Washington Square and University College, 1930-1984
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1930-1984 (Box 421, Folder 5)
- RG 40.20. Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1988-1989
  - Epilog, 1989 (Box 421, Folder 6)
  - Lions, 1988 (Box 420, Folder 8)
- RG 40.21.12. Department of Journalism, 1988-1991
  - News at 10, 1988-1991 (Box 421, Folder 7)
- RG 40.23.8. Veterinary College, 1917-1920
  - Alumni News, 1917-1920 (Box 421, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary Bulletin, 1917-1920 (Box 421, Folder 9-10, Box 422, Folder 1)
- RG 40.38. Institute of Fine Arts, 1976-2015
  The Institute of Fine Arts is dedicated to graduate teaching and advanced research in the history of art, archaeology, and the conservation and technology of works of art.
  - IFA Alumni Newsletter, 1988-2004 (Box 422, Folder 2-3)
  - IFA News, 1976 (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    The Twitter feed contains tweets related to exhibition openings, conferences, art colloquiums, alumni news, conservation news, commencement, excavation news, speaker series, contemporary art, digital art history, faculty research, the IFA slide collection and image archive, art tours, Great Hall exhibitions, and other events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990-2001 (Box 422, Folder 5)
- RG 42.4. Gallery of Living Art, 1927-1933, 1937
  - Catalogue, 1927-1933, 1937 (Box 422, Folder 6-8, Box 423, Folder 1)
- RG 42.5. Grey Art Gallery and Study Center, 1976-2019
  - Grey Art Gallery Bulletin, 1978-1989 (Box 423, Folder 2)
  - Grey Gazette, 1998, 2000-2012 (Box 423, Folder 3, Box 342, Folder 8, Box 420)
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1976-2019 (Box 423, Folder 4-8, Box 424, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera -- Posters, 1986-1988 (Box 344, Folder 4)
- RG 42.6. 80 Washington Square East Gallery, 1978-2015
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1978-2015 (Box 424, Folder 3-9, Box 425, Folder 1-9, Box 426, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera -- Washington Square Windows, 1997-2008 (Box 426, Folder 3-7)
- RG 42.7. Broadway Windows, 1985-2009
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1985-2009 (Box 426, Folder 8-10, Box 427, Folder 1-5)
- RG 42.8. NYU Art Collection, 1960-1973
  - New York University Art Collection, 1969-1973 (Box 427, Folder 6)
  - New York University Art Collection Catalog, 1960-1973 (Box 428, Folder 1-7)
- RG 42.9. The Bronfman Center for Jewish Life Galleries at NYU, 1999-2002
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1999-2002 (Box 429, Folder 1)
- RG 42.10. Kimmel Windows, 2008-2015
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2008-2015 (Box 429, Folder 2)
- RG 42.11. The Mamdouha S. Bobst Gallery, 2002-2010
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2002-2010 (Box 429, Folder 3)
- RG 42.12. Rosenberg Gallery, 1995
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1995 (Box 429, Folder 4)
- RG 42.13. Stovall Family Gallery, 2016
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2016 (Box 429, Folder 5)
- RG 43.3. Army Air Force Technical Training Command (AAFTTC), 1943
  - Bronx Cheer, 1943 (Box 429, Folder 6)
- RG 43.4. Army Specialized Training Unit (ASTU), 1943-1945
  - Ten Minute Break, 1943-1945 (Box 429, Folder 7)
- RG 44.0. Student Governance, 1970
  - Students and the Governance of NYU, 1970 (Box 429, Folder 8)
- RG 44.0.1. Student Senators Council, 2002-2003
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2002-2003 (Box 429, Folder 9)
- RG 44.4. Inter-Club Council (BPA), 1988-1989
  - Inter-Club Council Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 429, Folder 10)
- RG 44.5. BPA Student Council, 1987-1988
  - BPA Student Council Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 429, Folder 11)
  - Stern Student Council Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 429, Folder 12)
- RG 45.23. Ultra Violet, 1991
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 1991 (Box 429, Folder 13)
- RG 48.0. Polytechnic Institute of NYU / Tandon School of Engineering, 2014-2019
  Tandon was formerly known as the Polytechnical School of Engineering and changed its name in 2015.
  - Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology News, May 2014-May 2016
    Blog for the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology at the Tandon School of Engineering (at the time of capture Tandon was known as the Polytechnic School of Engineering). The blog contains posts related to books by faculty, archives, engineering, management and finance, mathematics, scholarly publishing, science, tips and tools, technology, culture, society, and other library news. The blog dates back to 2007.
  - Cable, May 2014-April 2019
    The alumni publication of Polytechnic School of Engineering (formerly Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn).
  - Polytechnic School of Engineering Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Polytechnic Institute of New York University. Includes posts related to faculty achievements, conferences, admissions, alumni news, start-ups, women in engineering, and news and events.
  - Polytechnic School of Engineering Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed of the NYU Polytechnic School of Engineering. Contains tweets related to admissions, job opportunities, start-ups, engineering, entrepreneurship, bitcoin, women in engineering, conferences, the Urban Future Lab, and other news and events.
  - Pulse, 2019 (Box 429, Folder 14)
  - Tandon School of Engineering in the Media, May 2014-May 2018
    Listing of media articles that mention Tandon or Tandon faculty. The articles date back to 2009.
  - Tandon School of Engineering News, May 2014-May 2018
    News from the Tandon School of Engineering. News dates back to 2005.
  - Tandon School of Engineering Research News, May 2014-May 2018
    Research News is a bulletin highlighting research and publications by the School of Engineering faculty and students.
  - Women in STEM Newsletters, May 2021